<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New Zealand Open Research Network</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on New Zealand Open Research Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/resources/</guid>
      <description>Open Research Resources:The Australia/New Zealand Open Research Network project on the Open Science Framework is an excellent place to go for resources relating to open research practices. You can find resources for Learning R (an open source language for statistical computing), podcasts relating to open research, statistical power calculators, reading lists, and syllabi for teaching open and reproducible practices.
Another great set of resources is the Open Science Toolbox hosted by the LMU Open Science Centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interim Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/code_of_conduct/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code_of_conduct/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>SummaryThe New Zealand Open Research Network (NZORN) seeks to promote open practices, and as part of this vision is committed to the provision of a safe, inclusive, welcoming and harassment-free atmosphere to all. All parties to activities associated with the Network are required to be compliant with the code of conduct. If you observe something that you do not feel is consistent with these principles, please report them to the steering committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re live!</title>
      <link>/blog/were_live/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/were_live/</guid>
      <description>The New Zealand Open Research Network website is now live. This is just a placeholder for the moment - blog posts will come in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massey University Affect, Cognition &amp; Environment cluster</title>
      <link>/portfolio/massey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 16:54:54 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/massey/</guid>
      <description>Massey University Affect, Cognition &amp;amp; Environment cluster Massey University is a New Zealand University spread across three campuses (Auckland, Wellington, and Palmerston North). There is a strong concentration of researchers interested in Open Science issues at the School of Psychology in the Affect, Cognition and Environment (ACE) research cluster.
Let&amp;rsquo;s add information about communities at more New Zealand universities here - get in touch via Twitter to have your university added.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>